def get_questions():
    return [{
        "question": "What is the output of 'print(2 + 2 * 3)' in Python?",
        "options": ["1. 8", "2. 10", "3. 6", "4. 12"],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a valid variable name in Python?",
        "options": ["1. my_variable", "2. 1_variable", "3. _variable", "4. variable_1"],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of '3 < 4 and 5 > 3' in Python?",
        "options": ["1. True", "2. False", "3. Error", "4. None"],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is used to comment out a single line in Python?",
        "options": ["1. //", "2. #", "3. --", "4. /* */"],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What method is used to remove the last item from a list in Python?",
        "options": ["1. pop()", "2. remove()", "3. del()", "4. clear()"],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What will be the output of 'print(len('python'))' in Python?",
        "options": ["1. 5", "2. 6", "3. 7", "4. 8"],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the 'range()' function in Python return?",
        "options": ["1. List", "2. Tuple", "3. Set", "4. Range object"],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct way to open a file 'file.txt' in Python for writing?",
        "options": ["1. open('file.txt', 'r')", "2. open('file.txt', 'w')", "3. open('file.txt', 'a')", "4. open('file.txt', 'x')"],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 'bool([])' in Python?",
        "options": ["1. True", "2. False", "3. Error", "4. None"],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the output of 'print('Python'[2:])' in Python?",
        "options": ["1. 'Py'", "2. 'th'", "3. 'Pyt'", "4. 'thon'"],
        "answer": 4
    }]

prize_levels = [1000, 2000, 3000, 5000, 10000, 20000, 30000, 40000, 80000, 160000, 320000, 640000, 1250000, 2500000, 500000, 10000000, 70000000]
stage_one = 10000
stage_two = 320000
